in this video I'm going to be showing
you how you can get access to all my
YouTube Secrets everything I use to get
over 100 million views a video and the
answer is my brand new website that I
just launched views.com so if you go to
views.com you'll see this right here and
you can enter in any YouTube channel you
want I'm going to put in Mr Beast my
channel boom and when you search a
channel it will pull up their Channel
page which basically allows you to see
the analytics of any channel another
thing you can see on a Channel's
analytics page that I don't think you
can find anywhere else on the Internet
is you can see how many views on that
channel are coming from long form versus
short form let's say a Channel's popping
off and getting a billion views a month
well if they're getting a billion views
a month from short that is completely
different than if they're getting a
billion views a month from long form and
so being able to distinguish the
difference is huge and everything you
see there is just the beginning because
if you hit this videos tab here you can
click on any video on my channel we'll
just do this ages 1 through 100 decides
video you can see the daily viewership
for specifically that video right here
and you can see every time we Swit the
thumbnails with this little icon of ab
thumbnail test on top of that you can
see what it ranked out of 10 no joke you
just click here and then it will show
you that that video is 4 out of 10 so
without view stats if you wanted to see
out of 10 how well a video performed on
a channel you couldn't unless you had
access to their creator Studio but now
you can see any video on all of YouTube
what it ranks out of 10 which I thought
was pretty cool on top of that you can
also see every single AV thumbnail test
ran on that video the next tab is called
similar channels and this is insane this
tab takes your content okay and it looks
at all the titles and the content you're
making and then it Compares it across
our giant data set and shows you other
channels that make similar content to
you that way if you're looking for
someone to collab or you just want to
get some inspiration off of people who
make similar content it is incredibly
easy and we didn't just stop there
basically if you go up to the top of
view stats you can hit Top subscribers
and what it will show you in real time
is the most subscribed to YouTube
channels on the platform and obviously
you can see the most viewed YouTube
channels those are pretty standard but
where it gets very cool you can also see
the top 50 most videos from the previous
day you can also see the most of videos
on the whole platform in the last 7 days
last 28 days even and this is crazy the
last year those are all the top charts
we currently offer and we're working
tirelessly to get more up here we also
have a view stats Chrome extension that
if you go to the Chrome Store and type
in view stats all you have to do is hit
add to Chrome just like any other
extension hit ADD extension and once you
install it whenever you're watching
Youtube you'll have this view stats
overlay to the right of the video and if
you look on the right side of the video
now you you'll see an overlay on the
video that shows you the daily
viewership of the video you can hit
compare compare it to my most recent
video on my channel you can hit ranking
and see what it ranked out of 10 when I
uploaded it you can see the overview of
my channel and so much more all without
having to leave YouTube everything I've
showed you so far is 100% free but we
didn't just stop here we wanted to build
some even crazier tools that we're
putting behind view stats Pro because
these things literally cost millions of
dollars to operate and I can't afford to
give them away for free on the free site
with everything else and view stats Pro
is going to blow your mind and I'm going
to explain it to you now the first tool
I want to show you guys is called
outliers and what outlier means is if
you have a Channel with let's say 10,000
subscribers and they get 100 views on
their first video 100 views on their
second video but their fourth video gets
100,000 views that fourth video got a
thousand times the views of the other
three videos it didn't just go viral
randomly it either was a good title
thumbnail the content something
something about that video was special
that caused it to do multiples better
than the channel average which is why we
label that in outlier and we store all
of them here so you can use them for
inspiration on top of that we built a
very robust filtering system you can say
I only want to see outliers that have
over a million views on channels over
100,000 subscribers that did at least
10x the average views on that channel in
the last 90 days that was a lot of
filters and boom look at how quick that
loaded and all those parameters are now
in place we went all out on this outlier
tool to make it as easy as possible for
you to just brainstorm viral ideas and
grow your viewership now I'm going to
show you the second tool on view stats
Pro and I got to sit up for this one cuz
it's going to blow your mind okay I
don't even know how we built this it's
called thumbnail search and you can type
in whatever you want and it will pull up
thumbnails for you to get inspired off
of okay let's say I'm a farmer and I
want to do a video on my tractor I'm
just going to type in something very
descriptive a person standing next to a
tractor right let's say I filmed a video
of my tractor and I want thumbnail
inspiration all you got to do is hit
enter and then boom this will show you
every thumbnail on YouTube that has a
person standing next to a tractor I
think this thumbnail right here that I'm
hovering my mouse over it's pretty
interesting and so what I'm going to do
is I'm going to hit search by thumbnail
and now it's going to pull up a bunch of
other thumbnails that were similar to
that giant tractor thumbnail in this
hypothetical scenario where I'm role
playing as a farmer making a video on my
tractor I now have good inspiration on
how I could angle the camera to make the
tractor look big and on what would do
well also you don't have to type in
something you can also just search by an
image and if you're ever on YouTube and
you see a thumbnail you like you can
just copy the URL to the video and paste
it there and search with that thumbnail
as well we thought of every single use
case and put it all into here the third
tool behind view stats Pro is called AB
test and what you're looking at now is
every single AB thumbnail test currently
being ran on YouTube we all know about
AB thumbnail tests you upload a couple
thumbnail options YouTube tests them all
out and it tells you which one's the
best and why I think this tool would be
valuable for you guys is instead of you
having to run dozens or hundreds or
thousands of ab thumbnail test across
all your videos on the channel to learn
about what people want and don't want
what if instead you could just see every
single AB thumbnail test every other
YouTuber is running and you can just
study those and apply their findings to
your channel and save a ton of time you
can type into this search bar whatever
you want let's say Minecraft you know if
you're a Minecraft Creator and this will
show you all the most recent AB
thumbnail tests ran on Minecraft
channels so we can scroll through here
looks like Preston ran an a thumbnail
test he tried this Blood Blaze forgot
son blood farm and it looks like
forgotten Sun one so I'm going to type
in Ryan trean my boy Ryan how you doing
his newest video is I tried every seat
on the most expensive Airline these were
his three thumbnail options he had 24/7
service with him laying in a bed he had
sleep pod $54 and then he had economy
slfirst class and the winner was the
economy first class one which the
interesting part about this tool is if
you went to my channel I did a similar
video like this like a year before he
did and if you look at our AB thumbnail
test the split in half economy first
class one also won for me so this is an
example how Ryan could have looked at my
ab thumbnail test saw what worked and
applied it to his channel and saved time
and you can see every single one of
these tests with view stats Pro and
learn from the millions of dollars I
spent making these thousands of
thumbnails and testing them on my
channel our fourth view stats pro tool
is alerts this one's a little more
straightforward than the other ones but
incredibly useful if you use it
correctly you can set an alert for
anything you'd want let's say I know
later this year I'm going to do a video
where I bu the world's largest treehouse
I can create an alert with the title I
built I'll set it where it shows me
anytime my video gets over a million
views I just want long not shorts and
then I hit create and then what it will
do is it will show me every video on all
of YouTube that has over a million views
with ibuilt in the title currently and
then it will alert me in the future
anytime another video meets that
threshold you can use this so if
something happens in your Niche or
vertical or whatever you're in real time
updated and you don't have to live on
YouTube our fifth tool is collection
which basically ties all the other tools
together in one spot let's say when
you're using the outlier tools you like
an idea you just hit this thing in the
top right of the idea and then you just
hit add new collection title It Whatever
Minecraft and basically whether you're
using alerts thumbnail search outliers
it allows you to store all the data that
you're finding across view stats Pro and
one spot for later and we're not just
stopping with these five tools with view
stats Pro we have over a dozen tools
that we're planning on launching over
the next year click the link in
description or go to views.com Ford SL
Pro I feel like a weight is now off my
shoulder we've been working on this for
so long and to finally launch all these
tools just H I just can't wait to hear
what you guys think of it